[{"answer": "Well, probably not, Piers, you know, they have it under control.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Can it get a lot worse pretty quickly?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't know but there's some great preachers in this country and some great men of God and I'm sure God will raise up somebody.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Did you see anybody who is anywhere near the mantel of your father to take up that kind of spiritual leadership in America?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "My father has preached the same message and that's God's Gospel.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What would you think in a best way of articulating his legacy should be?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "RUMP: Well, you know, you shake hands with somebody but he always seems to bow to foreign leaders.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "All over the papers today and the TV, for first of all this handshake, very deliberate with Raul Castro the Cuban President, are you supportive with that or are you against it?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Well, and his wife was not happy or she seemed like she wasn't too happy.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "And the selfie picture with him and the Danish Prime Minister and the British Prime Minister?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, it seems like the website really brought it to light how bad it all is.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Yeah, and it's been a disastrous rollout -- just from business point of view put me old business tycoon hat on, if he's going to carry on with it as he clearly is, what should he be doing to at least try and rescue the situation?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, it was a lie.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "... was he that, \"You can keep your plan and you can keep your doctor\" turned out to be a complete falsehood?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "But you know, Piers, I'm a developer.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "But only in the situation Donald where the very rich and successful elite perhaps in America are reveling in the current situation because money is cheaper there's plenty of it from this kind of thing that you want to do but for the vast majority of Americans, it's still very tough out there?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "It's hard to believe, and if you look at what's happening with China and some -- and I've been talking about this for years what China is doing to this country, they are outsmarting us in a business sense every single step ...", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "And if you look at what China is doing, they are steam rolling ahead here, 1.3 billion people being educated in a better and better way, you know, it doesn't look good does it for America in 30 years time in terms of the world stage?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "RUMP: You know, it's funny, in this building, I have the biggest bank in the world from China.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "I mean, you have to admire the Chinese?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "I think he is so refreshing.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "In other words for any institution is that what it needs?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well I think he's got a lot of great legacies.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Yeah, very sadly, I know that you saw him recently at a big event to celebrate his life, what would be his great legacy, Billy Graham?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Well it's an amazing story because to be in jail for like 27 years and to come out and be a man of not only humility but he sort of -- I was reading where during the inauguration, he had his jailer sitting on the front row and he was friendly to him.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "When you look at Mandela and I know that you had the honor of meeting him as I did, what do you make of him and the struggle that he came through?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well I think it's a great thing for America.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "You have a very smart woman working for you, your daughter Ivanka, do you see young successful women now all over the place in your trade and do you think it's good thing for Americans to be more running top companies like this?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well you don't want to do anything that's going to keep the incentive away for whether it's McDonalds that are expanding in this country.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "You employ a lot of people, thousands of people, are you in favor of raising the minimum wage?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "We need leadership.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What do you want to see happen?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I don't carry a wallet, I have very little cash on me, I like to keep it that way.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Do you carry your wallet and do you carry cash?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I don't do a lot of e-mail, I don't like e-mail.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Warren has sent one e-mail in his life, do you e-mail personally?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Do you use a cellphone?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well I have Apple and I have Samsung and I have a lot of stock in Apple and I want them to do a bigger screen because I do like the bigger Samsung screen and so far they haven't been listening to me.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Which mobile do you have?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "You know I have friends that swear by Blackberry, like you.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Is there really hope for Blackberry people like me?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, New York like the country is in big trouble but I'll be making decisions after January, we'll see what happens.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Any truth to that?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "You can straighten these things out, it wouldn't be hard to straighten New York out at, it wouldn't be so hard to straighten the country at.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Are you tempted?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "When he grabbed me -- say, this was my foot and the shark grabbed me, the top teeth is like serrated knives and the lower teeth, they're like forks.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "And what is the prognosis for a quick speed recovery?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, I was a bit perplexed and surprised until I read the history of how he came about this decision to do the film.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What did you feel when you first heard about this?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "As presidents and senators often say, \"I misspoke\", I think the choice of the word chauvinist did not really accurately reflect what was going on.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "... doesn't carry much credit, isn't it?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I was pretty persistent.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Were you a guy that just never gave up on a good story?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Only in a few interviews this week but not -- no.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Have you ever used the words, \"Stay classy San Diego\"?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Well, of course.", "docId": "131211pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Would you mind just humoring me more and just ending this interview with those immortal words as if you were Ron Burgundy?", "qSentId": 542}]